Hi, my name is Rebecca, I'm 43 years of age, and I have been with Blueprint since May last year,
suffered with mobility issues for a number of years, that progressively got worse and worse,
to the point where I needed help to get out of bed, I couldn't stand up properly,
I fell over a lot. When I finally got diagnosed, such as last year, I had the diagnosis of
young onset Parkinson's and also dystonia, which makes my certain parts of my body
and sees up. The first thing was getting the hang of the medication. The second thing,
and also the most important thing, was for me to get moving again. So I joined Blueprint,
and from being a person who needed physical help to even get out of the bed in the morning,
I now have come down, I've done my barbell class today with no medicine in my body,
I've been able to walk, I can feel the benefits of coming here. My muscles are working in a much
special way, they're supporting me, I don't fall half as much as I did before.
If somebody like me can come down to a place like this, where you're surrounded by not only
coaches that give you unbelievable support and advice, but also a community where people are
patting you on the back and telling you that you're amazing. In regardless of your situation,
I see you go, give it a go guys.